>> 凯尔: 那么 ToNumber 怎么办 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So what about ToNumber?
这件更有趣的地方还有更多的角处
This one's a bit more interesting cuz
there's a lot more corner cases involved.
如果我们需要做点数字而我们没有数字
Anytime we need to do something
numeric and we don't have a number,
我们要调用 ToNumber 抽象操作
we're gonna invoke the ToNumber
abstract operation.
那么，这些人的例子是什么呢 ?
So what are some examples of those?
有些是很不错的，但有些很奇怪。
Some of them are well formed,
but some of them are strange.
我认为空的字符串是最让我最幸运的一个。
Empty string, I think, is the one
that drives me the most bonkers.
空字符串，每当数字化，或
Empty string, whenever numericofied, or
不管用什么正确的词都变成了 0
whatever the right word would be for
that, becomes 0.
就我所关心的
Now as far as I'm concerned,
空字符串是您说我在字符串中没有值的方式。
empty string is the way that you
say I have no values in a string.
在该类型中不存在任何字符串值。
It's the absence of any string
value within that type.
不存在字符串类型中缺少值的其他表示，
There's no other representation of the
absence of values within the string type,
除了空的字串我还能看出来
other than an empty string,
as far as I can tell.
所以如果没有价值，为什么在地球上，当它变成一个数字时，
So if it's the absence of value, why on
Earth does it, when it becomes a number,
成为实际数字，如数字 0 ，而不是已存在的数字
become an actual number like the number 0
instead of the number that already exist
在语言中，表示我们没有有效的号码?
in the language, that represents
we don't have a valid number?
那是 NaN
Which would have been NaN.
我在这一点上就在这一点因为事实证明了
I'm ranting on this particular
point because it turns out,
我们会看到那是 JavaScript中所有邪恶的根源
we're gonna see that's the root
of all evil in JavaScript.
但大部分其他的都是非常明智的。
But most of the rest of
these are all very sensible.
如果您有字符串 0，那么它将变为 0。
If you had the string 0, it becomes 0.
如果你有一个字符串 -0 ，这是一个意外，它实际上变成了 -0，
If you had the string -0,
here's a surprise, it actually becomes -0,
非常酷
very cool.
它会去掉任何领先的空格，尾部空格，以及
It strips off any leading white space,
trailing whitespace, and
所以我们只需要 9个
leading zeros, so we just get 9.
它能很好地处理浮点数。
It handles floating points well.
一些古怪的线索和线索
Some weirdness with the trailing and
leading dots, but
这些都在语法上有效。
those are syntactically valid.
它甚至可以处理其他的碱基，比如这个例子，十六进制。
It even handles other's bases,
like in this case, hexadecimal.
我不知道这个词应该是什么
So the numerification,
I don't know what that word should be,
一个字符串值是相当合理的，有几个奇怪的角个案。
of a string value is fairly sensible,
with a couple of weird corner cases.
如何处理谬误的数字或
What about dealing with
the numerification of falses or
truees， nulls 或 undefined ?
trues, or nulls or undefined?
那些原始的人呢
What about those other primitives?
那么 false 变为 0， true 变为 1。
Well, false becomes 0, true becomes 1.
从一开始，你也许会想，这完全有道理。
And at the outset, you might think,
well, that makes complete sense.
从历史上我们一直认为错误是 0
Historically, we've always
thought of false as being 0 and
值为 1，从位角度来看。
true as being 1,
from bit-wise perspective.
我要走了我要把脚放下来说这主意糟透了
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna put my foot
down and say that was a terrible idea,
如果数字应该表示为 NaN，那么表示 false 和 true 。
that false and true, when represented as
numbers should have represented as NaN.
你会知道为什么以后会这样
And you'll see why a little bit later.
但我不喜欢这个决定
But that, I don't like that decision.
但我明白为什么在更大的编程范围内
But I understand why,
within the context of greater programming,
这可能是大多数人所期待的
that's probably what
most people would expect.
空值为 0，好吗 ?
Null becomes 0, okay?
但未定义的是 NaN ，什么?
But undefined becomes NaN, what?
在这里他们决定最后使用 NaN ，但它们不使用 NN吗 ?
Here they decided to finally use NaN,
but they didn't use it with null?
有人向我解释
Somebody explain that one to me.
NaN 应该是 NN，就像 NNaN 一样。
Null should have been NaN,
just like undefined should have been NaN.
好吧当我们在非原始的非原始状态下使用 ToNumber 时
Okay, so when we use ToNumber on
a nonprimitive that's not a string,
或者不是一个没有定义的，或者是一个布尔值什么的，当我们在一个物体中使用它的时候，
or not an undefined, or a boolean or
whatever, when we use it in an object,
记得它用数字提示唤起了托普里米蒂
remember it evokes the ToPrimitive
with the number hint.
如果你还记得那就先把 valueOf
And if you recall,
that consults first the valueOf, and
然后它会咨询 toString。
then it consults the toString.
那么这看起来是什么样的呢 ?
So what does that look like?
那么对于任何数组或对象，缺省情况下，表示您
Well, for any array or object,
by default, meaning you
未覆盖这些值， valueOf 方法本质上仅返回自身。
have not overridden these, the valueOf
method essentially just returns itself.
它本质上就是这样，把它退回去。
It essentially does this, return this.
这会影响仅忽略 toString 的 valueOf 和 dexing 。
Which has the affect of just ignoring
the valueOf and deferring to toString.
所以即使提示是数字也不重要。
So it doesn’t even matter
that the hint was number.
它直接转至 toString。
It just goes directly to the toString.
你可以想象一个物体的数字化
You can think of the numberification
of an object as,
本质上，它的平化。
essentially, the stringification of it.
它会产生产生任何 toString 或 valueOf 的产品。
It's that it's gonna end up producing
whatever toString or valueOf produces.
那是个变态的选择但还是选择
That's a perplexing choice, but
it's the choice nonetheless,
它会产生一个原始的字符串
is that it's gonna actually
produce a primitive string.
所以在你的各种行动中你预期会有一个原始的
So then in your various operations where
you were expecting a primitive, but
你想要一个原始的数字实际上这里有一个原始的字符串
you wanted a primitive number,
there's actually a primitive string there.
然后就会有更多的强迫
And then further coersions will kick in.
所以我们要推迟到 toString
So we're gonna end up
deferring to the toString and
任何 toString 返回的内容。
whatever the toString returns.
记住如何在没有任何方括号的情况下对自己进行排列。
Remember how arrays toStringify
themselves without any brackets.
因此，我们会得到一个数组，其中包含空字符串。
So again, we get an array
with an empty string in it.
当我们 ToNumber 它的时候，它就成了 0，是疯了。
When we ToNumber it,
it ends up as 0, which is nuts.
然后，在其中包含 0 的字符串变为 0 更有意义。
And then the string with 0 in it,
becoming 0 makes a lot more sense.
- 0 比我更有道理
And -0 makes a lot more sense.
太离奇了
Here's something bizarre.
如果数组为空或未定义，那么它将变为 0。
If the array has either null or
undefined, it becomes 0.
看看你是否需要注意
See if you're paying attention.
谁能告诉我为什么这两个人都成了 0
Can anyone tell me why both
of those become 0 here?
>> 扬声器 2: 与以下项的其余部分不一致 -
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Not consistent
with the rest of the-
>> 凯尔: 实际上，这很明显
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Actually, this is remarkably
与我们已经看到的其他疯狂的情况相符
consistent with the other
craziness we've already seen.
>> 扬声器 3: 因为它们首先成为空字符串吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Because they
first become empty strings?
>> 凯尔: 它们首先变为空字符串，然后空字符串变为 0。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: They first become empty strings,
and then empty string becomes 0.
记住空弦是所有高压恶魔的根
Remember, empty string is the root
of all coercion evil, okay?
空字符串变成 0 是所有强制邪恶的根源，好吗 ?
Empty string becoming 0 is the root
of all coercion evil, okay?
跟那个最底层疯狂的嵌套阵列一样
Same thing with that bottom
crazy nested array thing,
就变成了一个空的字符串，就变成 0了，好吗 ?
it just becomes an empty string,
which then just becomes 0, okay?
>> 凯尔: 好的，如果您有对象，那么它的 toString 将返回对象。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: All right, so if you have an
object, its toString returns the object.
还记得默认情况下一个对象的干姜是什么
And remember what a stringification
of an object by default is,
就是那个方形支架对象物
it's that square bracket
object object thing.
这绝对不是一个数字的代表，所以我们得到 NaN。
Which is definitely not a representation
of a number, so we get NaN.
这才是合理的
That's actually reasonable.
太傻了但这很合理
It's dumb, but it's reasonable.
如果您覆盖某个对象的值，
If you override the valueOf for
some object,
你可以把你想要的东西都退回去
you can return whatever thing you want.
在这种情况下，你可以返回 3 ，这就是它的编号。
In this case, you could return 3, and
that's the numberification for it.